https://www.sensesofcinema.com/privacy/

Search
Subscribe to Senses of Cinema to receive news of our latest cinema journal.Enter your email address below:
Submit
Search
Privacy
SENSES OF CINEMA PRIVACY POLICY
www.sensesofcinema.com is operated by or on behalf of Senses of Cinema Inc. (ABN 27 223 441 751) (“Senses of Cinema”). This policy sets out how Senses of Cinema manages your personal information through adopting the 13 Australian Privacy Principles under Schedule 1 of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and other laws, which protect your privacy.
YOUR INFORMATION
The names and email addresses entered in this journal site will be used exclusively for the stated purposes of this journal and will not be made available for any other purpose or to any other party.
When referring to ‘personal information’, we mean information that identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your name or pseudonym, your postal address or email address and/or your phone number are examples of personal information.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
The only information that we collect about you when you use the Senses of Cinema website is what you tell us about yourself, for example, when you submit feedback to us and provide your name or pseudonym and email address or other personal details. If you receive email communications from us, you will always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving such emails.
In common with many websites, when you read, browse or download information from our website, we or our internet service provider may also collect information such as the date and time of your visit to the website, the pages accessed and any information downloaded. This information is used for statistical, reporting and website administration, maintenance and improvement purposes only.
Like many websites, our Website may use ‘cookies’ from time to time. Cookies are small text files that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser. Cookies may also be used to record non-personal information such as the date, time or duration of your visit, or the pages accessed, for website administration, statistical and maintenance purposes. Any such information will be aggregated and not linked to particular individuals. The default settings of browsers like Internet Explorer always allow cookies, but users can easily erase cookies from their hard-drive, block all cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please note that some parts of the Website may not function fully for users that disallow cookies.
USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
We may collect, use and exchange your information so that we can:
Establish your identity and assess applications for products and services;
Communicate with you on all things Senses of Cinema;
Email you e-newsletters or other updates (if you have requested to receive them). If you decide that you no longer want to receive such updates from us, you will have the ability to unsubscribe; and
Conduct and improve the Senses of Cinema website and improve the user experience.
This is not an exhaustive list. We may also collect, use and exchange your information in other ways where permitted or required by law.
DIRECT MARKETING
We may also use your information so that we can promote and market the Senses of Cinema business, services and special offers that we think will be of interest to you. This marketing may be carried out in a variety of ways, including by email, social media or by customising online content and displaying advertising on websites and may continue until you unsubscribe or contact admin@sensesofcinema.com to opt out.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
Senses of Cinema uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilises the data collected to track and examine the use of www.sensesofcinema.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
Irrespective of whether personal information is stored electronically or in hard copy form, we take reasonable steps to protect the personal information we hold from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.
ACCESSING AND UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
To make a request to access or correct any personal information we hold about you, please contact us via email at admin@sensesofcinema.com.
Please provide us with as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged where permitted by law. In certain circumstances, we may not be required by law to provide you with access or to correct your personal information. If that is the case, we will give you our reasons for that decision.
We take reasonable steps to make sure that the personal information we collect, use and disclose is accurate, complete and up-to-date.
FURTHER INFORMATION
The Senses of Cinema website may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of those sites.
We may need to change this Policy. If we do, we will post the updated version on the Senses of Cinema website. Please also note that during the course of our relationship with you, we may tell you more about how we handle your information.
MAKING A PRIVACY COMPLAINT
You may contact us at admin@sensesofcinema.com to notify us of any privacy complaint you have against us, including if you think we have failed to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles. You may also lodge a complaint with a relevant regulator such as the Australian Information Commissioner via www.oaic.gov.au.
Read the Senses of Cinema World Poll 2019
INTRODUCTION
PART 1
PART 2
PART 3
PART 4
PART 5
PART 6
